John one of the things I wanted to talk
to you about is your own case because uh
people know that you a whistleblower but
people may not know that there's been a
kind of bipartisan uh refusal to Pardon
you for whistleblowing and I it's
disgusting you blew the whistle on the
CIA torture program and the idea that
the only person to pay a price is the
person not who engaged in the torture
but blew the whistle on it can you shed
a little bit of light on the pardon
process I applied for a pardon with
Barack Obama I was ignored I knew I
would be then I applied for pardon from
Donald Trump in Trump's first term Rudy
Giuliani tried to shake me down for $2
million and I ratted him out to the New
York Times but I got that close because
Tucker Carlson helped me then on the
last day of the Trump presidency Tucker
called me and said that Mitch McConnell
had said that if Trump pardoned and this
was the original idea Assange and
Snowden that he couldn't control the
Republican caucus in the Senate and that
they would probably vote to convict him
on the impeachment charges then I go to
Biden I'm friendly with a Greek Orthodox
priest who is very very close to Joe
Biden he said I can help you so I'm
getting you know this guy to write a
letter and that guy to write a letter
and Senator so and so and Congressman
what's his name and I got Annette
Benning and I got Susan Sarandon and I
got a whole Hollywood contingent and
then he passed me over and I said to the
priest well if I had been a crackhead or
a Chinese spy or a judge that sold
children into bondage maybe I would have
I would have gotten so [__] Joe Biden
excuse my language